http://www.ajckids.com/pages/privacy-and-cookie-policy

Menu
Cart 0
..
Wishlist (0)
Marklin Museum Cars
My World (ages 3 & up)
Roco Powered Railcars
Roco Diesel Engines (AC)
Roco Electric Engines (AC)
Roco Steam Locomotives (AC)
Roco Powered Railcars (AC)
Piko H0-Scale New Items 2020
Piko H0-Scale Locomotives (DC 2-Rail)
Piko H0-Scale Locomotives (AC 3-Rail)
Lokpilot Decoders
ESU Lokpilot H0-Scale V5.0 Decoders (no sound)
Marklin Museum Cars
My World (ages 3 & up)
Roco Powered Railcars
Roco Diesel Engines (AC)
Roco Electric Engines (AC)
Roco Steam Locomotives (AC)
Roco Powered Railcars (AC)
Piko H0-Scale New Items 2020
Piko H0-Scale Locomotives (DC 2-Rail)
Piko H0-Scale Locomotives (AC 3-Rail)
Lokpilot Decoders
ESU Lokpilot H0-Scale V5.0 Decoders (no sound)
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
Any personal information that we may collect, is information you send to us. So if you sign up for our mailing list, we collect your email address. This should make sense to most people. So we collect the following information (again, if submitted to us):
Your name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided, but only when you specifically sign up for our mail list. We hate spam and excess emails just as much as you do!
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail if we have questions related to your order.
Fax? Why don't you just send it over on a dinosaur?
- Michael Scott
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. Our website uses the highest level of security standards. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
Our website uses traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute, share or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
